Andrea Jared

St. Petersburg, Fl (330)280-7465 AndreaDJared@gmail.com ·

www.linkedin.com/in/Andrea-Jared https://github.com/adi0609

SUMMARY

Junior Full Stack Developer with experience with the MERN (MongoDB, ExpressJS, ReactJs, and NodeJs) tech stack. Recently Graduated Full Stack Development Bootcamp through the University of Central Florida with a graduation date of 17 November 2022. Familiar with OOP, API's, PWA, Stripe and version control with Git and GitHub. A self-starter and a team player with extensive experience in management and leadership from the service industry as a Director of Outlets managing multiple restaurants. Currently working with Automations suchs as wordpress, ClickFunnels, shopify and ActiveCampaign

Languages	<u>Databases</u>	Frameworks	<u>Platforms</u>	<u>CRMS</u>
JavaScript	NoSQL	REACT	Wordpress	ActiveCampaign
HTML	MondoDB	Handlebars	ClickFunnels	Zapier
CSS	MSSQL	NodeJs	Shopify	Monday.com
JQuery	MySQL	Node	Rainmaker AI	Hyros
				Looker Studio

Looker Studio

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

ROI MACHINES

OCTOBER 2022 - PRESENT

JUNIOR DEVELOPER/ TECH INTEGRATOR

- Creating Wordpress, Shopify and Clickfunnels Stores using Liquid, pagefly and elementor.
- Setting up email automations for marketing purposes using ActiveCampaign
- Hard coding Custom HTML, Javascript and css for creative purposes
- Set up and manage CRMs such as Monday.com and Looker Studios to pull data on each client
- Use Zaps to create a flow for projects that don't have direct integrations such as Clickfunnels and Shopify
- Manage Ad Tech Stacks and Create Automatic reporting systems for client facing reports
- Study new technologies for productivity
- Create 2 new Tech SOP each week

Troubleshoot and test client websites

UNIVERSITY OF CENTRAL FLORIDA

JUNE 2022 - NOVEMBER 2023

FULL STACK DEVELOPMENT STUDENT

- Completed the following projects:
- Created a food roulette game using HTML, CSS and JavaScript on the client-side and connected to server-side API's to randomize meal creations.
- Created a fully functional full stack blog using JavaScript and handlebars.js as a template for JavaScript functions, Express as the framework for NodeJs. Stored and persisted blog posts to MySQL database. The blog also contained roles, permission, and validations on the client side to include error handling.
- Completed the following challenges in key technical areas to include Web API's, third party API's, server-side API, ORM, MVC, RegEx.

LE MERIDIEN, TAMPA

FEBRUARY 2022 – August 2022

FOOD AND BEVERAGE DIRECTOR

- Successfully managed, led and supervised 40 employees across five restaurants to include managers and supervisors.
- Modernized operations for the five restaurants to include creating a new Standard Operating Procedure which resulted with a higher customer satisfaction rate.
- Decreased employee turnover by fostering a fun, productive and safe work environment.
- Trained and managed supervisors and managers on the new SOP, budgeting and operations.
- Managed budgeting for multiple restaurants and never exceeding set budgets
- Increased revenue from an otherwise failing restaurant within six months of My being there

ALOFT TAMPA DOWNTOWN

SEPTEMBER 2019-FEBRUARY 2022

FRONT OFFICE MANAGER

- Implemented a successful SOP to create a productive and organizational operation with staff to decrease turnover and unhealthy work environment.
- Trained staff to create a consistent and honest work and guest flow throughout the entire hotel.
- Managed budgeting for the rooms, bar, and lobby store and never exceeding set budgets.
- Coordinating with other departments to make sure rooms and other outlets are working in sync with one another creating a constant guest turnover.

A1 Japanese Steakhouse

AUGUST 2017-SEPTEMBER 2019

ASSISTANT GENERAL MANAGER

 Successfully managed a restaurant of 75 employees of a single restaurant including managers and supervisors.

2

- Decreased employee turnover by creating a fun, safe, knowledgeable and productive work environments.
- Worked closely with ownership to increase revenue, training SOP's and creativity within a stand-alone restaurant.
- Managed budgets from different revenue centers within the restaurant, decreasing spending and increasing productivity in purchasing.
- Trained managers and supervisors to instill an environment that ensured a successful business.

EDUCATION

June 2014

BUSINESS MANAGEMENT, STARK STATE UNIVERSITY

NOVEMBER 2022

CERTIFICATE IN FULL STACK DEVELOPMENT, UNIVERSITY OF CENTRAL FLORIDA